Pamela Gloria

(714) 717-6543 | pamela.o.gloria@gmail.com | Woodland Hills, CA

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented, problem solver with 460+ training hours of utilizing JavaScript to build responsive websites. Interested in attaining a career as a Front End Developer for an opportunity to showcase my creativity, excel as a web developer, as well as highlight my leadership abilities from previous work experience and knowledge in programming, marketing, and web development.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Novice: Backend (Java, SQL & Postman)
- Bilingual: Spanish & English
- Proactive self-starter
- Growth Mindset
- Strong organizational skills
- Excellent oral, written and listening communication skills

EXPERIENCE

Sodexo, Disneyland | June, 2017-August, 2021

Lead Cashier

• Performed ardently as a full-time cashier in a high-performance setting, handled multiple lead duties: delegated fellow coworkers' tasks according to their strengths and oversaw 3 stations at once

Sears & Roebok | November, 2016-January 2019

Lead Footwear Associate

• Operated in the footwear department as the Lead Retail Associate. Developed strategies to maintain inventory, kept records updated, provided excellent customer service, ordered and restocked merchandise.

EDUCATION

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | April 2022-August 2022 Participated in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasized hands-on practical application. Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3. Implementing basic unit tests